(function(){const o=document.createElement("link").relList;if(o&&o.supports&&o.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const n of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))i(n);new MutationObserver(n=>{for(const s of n)if(s.type==="childList")for(const k of s.addedNodes)k.tagName==="LINK"&&k.rel==="modulepreload"&&i(k)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function t(n){const s={};return n.integrity&&(s.integrity=n.integrity),n.referrerpolicy&&(s.referrerPolicy=n.referrerpolicy),n.crossorigin==="use-credentials"?s.credentials="include":n.crossorigin==="anonymous"?s.credentials="omit":s.credentials="same-origin",s}function i(n){if(n.ep)return;n.ep=!0;const s=t(n);fetch(n.href,s)}})();const H=[{id:1,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",options:["Standard notation","Tab notation","Morse code notation","Graphics notation"],answer:"Morse code notation",category:"music"},{id:2,question:"What is the most common time signature in classical music?",options:["3/4","4/4","5/4","6/8"],answer:"4/4",category:"music"},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",options:["Violin","Piano","Harp","Theremin"],answer:"Theremin",category:"music"},{id:4,question:"What is the most common key in pop music?",options:["C Major","G Major","D Major","A Major"],answer:"C Major",category:"music"},{id:5,question:"Which of the following is not a type of chord?",options:["Major","Minor","Diminished","Flat"],answer:"Flat",category:"music"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",options:["Jazz","Blues","Rock","Applesauce"],answer:"Applesauce",category:"music"},{id:7,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",options:["Harmony","Counterpoint","Form","Cooking"],answer:"Cooking",category:"music"},{id:8,question:"What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",options:["Allegro","Andante","Adagio","Moderato"],answer:"Allegro",category:"music"},{id:9,question:"Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",options:["Sonata","Symphony","Concerto","Spaghetti"],answer:"Spaghetti",category:"music"},{id:10,question:"Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",options:["Sibelius","Finale","MuseScore","Microsoft Word"],answer:"Microsoft Word",category:"music"}],J=[{id:21,question:"What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",options:["if (condition):","if condition","if: condition","if condition:"],answer:"if condition:",category:"coding"},{id:22,question:"Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",options:["String","Number","Boolean","ArrayList"],answer:"ArrayList",category:"coding"},{id:23,question:"Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",options:["var","let","const","int"],answer:"int",category:"coding"},{id:24,question:"What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",options:["for i = 0 to 10","for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)","for (int i = 0; i <= 10)","for i in range(0, 10)"],answer:"for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",category:"coding"},{id:25,question:"Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",options:["while","for","do-while","foreach"],answer:"foreach",category:"coding"},{id:26,question:"Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",options:["+","-","*","$"],answer:"$",category:"coding"},{id:27,question:"In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"Python",category:"coding"},{id:28,question:"What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",options:["function name()","def name","function name","def name()"],answer:"def name()",category:"coding"},{id:29,question:"Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",options:["Int","String","Double","Object"],answer:"Object",category:"coding"},{id:30,question:"In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",options:["Python","JavaScript","Java","C++"],answer:"C++",category:"coding"}],F={music:H,"modern-art":[{id:11,question:"Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:12,question:"Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Futurism","Cubism"],answer:"Cubism",category:"modern-art"},{id:13,question:"Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",options:["Pablo Picasso","Salvador Dali","Vincent van Gogh","Henri Matisse"],answer:"Salvador Dali",category:"modern-art"},{id:14,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",options:["Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Edvard Munch","Claude Monet"],answer:"Edvard Munch",category:"modern-art"},{id:15,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",options:["Impressionism","Expressionism","Fauvism","Cubism"],answer:"Fauvism",category:"modern-art"},{id:16,question:"What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",options:["Impressionism","Futurism","Surrealism","Abstract Expressionism"],answer:"Futurism",category:"modern-art"},{id:17,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",options:["Claude Monet","Paul Cezanne","Paul Gauguin","Paul Klee"],answer:"Claude Monet",category:"modern-art"},{id:18,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",options:["Henri Matisse","Vincent van Gogh","Salvador Dali","Pablo Picasso"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:19,question:"Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",options:["Claude Mone","Paul Cezanne","Pablo Picasso","Vincent van Gogh"],answer:"Pablo Picasso",category:"modern-art"},{id:20,question:"Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",options:["Auguste Rodin","Alexander Calder","Jean Arp","Henry Moore"],answer:"Auguste Rodin",category:"modern-art"}],coding:J};function j(e){let o=[];return e.forEach(t=>{o.push(t.answer)}),o}function E(e,o){for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let i=document.createElement("div"),n=document.createElement("input"),s=document.createElement("label");i.classList.add("option-item"),n.name="answer",n.type="radio",n.id=e[t],n.value=e[t],s.textContent=e[t],s.setAttribute("for",e[t]),i.appendChild(n),i.appendChild(s),o.appendChild(i)}}function O(e){let o=[];for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let i=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length);if(o.includes(e[i]))return O(e);o.push(e[i])}return o}function M(e){let o=[];for(let t=0;t<e.length;t++){let i=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length);if(o.includes(e[i]))return M(e);o.push(e[i])}return o}const G=document.querySelector(".navbar"),v=document.querySelector(".quiz-container"),Q=document.querySelector(".form-container"),y=document.querySelectorAll(".topic-item"),N=document.querySelectorAll(".topic-item .topic"),$=document.querySelector(".start-btn"),f=document.querySelector(".submit-btn"),S=document.querySelector(".quit-btn button"),V=document.querySelector(".play-again-btn"),I=document.querySelector(".topic-title"),p=document.querySelector(".question p"),u=document.querySelector(".options"),R=document.querySelector(".quiz"),q=document.querySelector(".time"),C=document.querySelector(".end-message .message"),x=document.querySelector(".final-result"),L=document.querySelector(".end-message"),U=document.querySelector(".result-btn"),Y=document.querySelector(".username"),g=document.querySelector(".alert"),z=document.querySelector(".alert p");localStorage.getItem("user")&&(Y.textContent=localStorage.getItem("user"));let c="",r="",b=[],d=[],m,h=15;function D(){for(let e=0;e<y.length;e++)y[e].addEventListener("click",()=>{document.querySelector(".selected")&&document.querySelector(".selected").classList.remove("selected"),y[e].classList.add("selected"),I.textContent=y[e].textContent+" Quiz",I.style.color="white",c=N[e].textContent.toLowerCase().split(" ").join("-"),c==="coding"&&(v.style.backgroundColor="#ffb703"),c==="modern-art"&&(v.style.backgroundColor="#023047"),c==="music"&&(v.style.backgroundColor="#219ebc"),r=F[c],r=O(r),d=j(r)})}function B(){if(c!==""){Q.classList.add("inactive"),G.classList.add("inactive"),p.textContent=r[l].question;let e=M(r[l].options);E(e,u),R.classList.add("active"),v.classList.remove("inactive"),m=setInterval(()=>{h===0&&(p.textContent="",u.innerHTML="",f.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.add("inactive"),L.classList.remove("inactive"),C.textContent="Oh! You went out of Time. Please Try Again.",clearInterval(m)),q.textContent=h--},1e3)}else{g.classList.remove("inactive"),z.textContent="Please Select a Topic",g.style.backgroundColor="red";let e=setTimeout(()=>{g.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(e)},3e3)}}D();let l=0;$.addEventListener("click",()=>{B()});f.addEventListener("click",()=>{let e=document.querySelectorAll(".active .options .option-item input"),o=!1;if(e.forEach(t=>{t.checked===!0&&(b.push(t.value),o=!0)}),console.log(b),console.log(d),o)if(l+1===r.length)p.textContent="",u.innerHTML="",f.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.add("inactive"),L.classList.remove("inactive"),C.textContent="Well Done! You answered All the Questions.",clearInterval(m),q.textContent=0;else{clearInterval(m),l++,p.textContent=r[l].question,u.innerHTML="";let t=M(r[l].options);E(t,u),h=15,m=setInterval(()=>{h===0&&(p.textContent="",u.innerHTML="",f.classList.add("inactive"),S.classList.add("inactive"),L.classList.remove("inactive"),C.textContent="Oh! You went out of Time. Please Try Again.",clearInterval(m)),q.textContent=h--},1e3)}else{g.classList.remove("inactive"),z.textContent="Please Select an Option",g.style.backgroundColor="red";let t=setTimeout(()=>{g.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(t)},3e3)}});U.addEventListener("click",()=>{let e=0;q.textContent=0,b.forEach((t,i)=>{t===d[i]&&e++}),x.textContent=`${e} out of ${d.length}`,x.style.color="green";let o=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("userTrack"));o?(localStorage.removeItem("userTrack"),localStorage.setItem("userTrack",JSON.stringify([{topic:c,userAnswer:e,totalScore:d.length,date:new Date().toLocaleString()},...o]))):localStorage.setItem("userTrack",JSON.stringify([{topic:c,userAnswer:e,totalScore:d.length,date:new Date().toLocaleString()}]))});V.addEventListener("click",()=>{l=0,h=15,b=[],f.classList.remove("inactive"),S.classList.remove("inactive"),L.classList.add("inactive"),x.textContent="",C.textContent="",D(),B()});const W=document.querySelector(".create-user-container"),P=document.querySelector(".sign-up-btn"),K=document.querySelector(".username"),A=document.querySelector(".user-form input"),X=document.querySelector(".text a"),Z=document.querySelector(".user-form .create-btn"),_=document.querySelector(".user-form .cancel-btn"),a=document.querySelector(".alert"),T=document.querySelector(".alert p");let w="";localStorage.getItem("user")&&P.classList.add("inactive");P.addEventListener("click",()=>{W.classList.remove("inactive")});A.addEventListener("change",()=>{w=A.value});Z.addEventListener("click",()=>{if(w!==""){W.classList.add("inactive"),localStorage.setItem("user",w),a.classList.remove("inactive"),T.textContent="User Created Successfully!",a.style.backgroundColor="green",P.classList.add("inactive"),K.textContent=w;let e=setTimeout(()=>{a.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(e)},3e3)}else{a.classList.remove("inactive"),T.textContent="Invalid Credentials!",a.style.backgroundColor="red";let e=setTimeout(()=>{a.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(e)},3e3)}});_.addEventListener("click",()=>{W.classList.add("inactive")});X.addEventListener("click",()=>{if(localStorage.getItem("user"))window.location.pathname="/quiz.html";else{a.classList.remove("inactive"),T.textContent="Please Create User",a.style.backgroundColor="red";let e=setTimeout(()=>{a.classList.add("inactive"),clearTimeout(e)},3e3)}});
